Today is our net night talk Chikan Kinoshita.
With Yuzuki.
I would like to introduce Yuzuki's character to you.
Thank you very much.
In the meantime, Yuzuki-chan...
Amelash's fake YouTube project
I've got a YouTube temp form for Amelash.
Oh! Thank you very much.
Actually, you know, we have a
We have a pre-determined
We're going to do a pre-determined work called
Yuzuki-chan to do the "Bukkomi Work".
Yuzuki-chan.
Ending
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Congratulations to me too.
I'm sure everyone will have the courage to shake it up and do it,
I will not let that courage go to waste, and I will also try to create an awkward atmosphere to the fullest extent.
Good luck!
Notice for next time
extra
5 seconds, 5 seconds, 1, 2, 3
and this is at least en line
Let's go with you and make it happen
I'm a brand new mind
Hear me now
Words
Then I don't need them anymore
It's a now, it's a vow
Dreams and destiny
Nice to meet you.
We have a little Mr. Oshiro here today.
Mr. Oshiro?
Who's Mr. Oshiro?
Mr. Oshiro.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What the hell.
Then, may we introduce you one more time?
Yes. So, I'm Yuzaki.
Yes, I'm Sayuki Oshiro.
I am Sayuki Oshiro. Pleased to meet you.
We have the same name, right?
I'm really sorry.
I'm a little sorry about Yuzaki.
I'm sorry. It's because we have the same name.
That's right.
Is that a member color?
Yes, it is.
Do you prefer mine?
No, it's not.
I still think you should fix it.
Can I fix it?
Yes, you can. No?
He's getting quiet.
Mr. Oodara is here today to answer any questions you may have.
I'm answering.
I'm glad. Anything?
What do you want to do?
May I start?
I've been wondering about this for a while,
I'm a fan of Yuzaki-chan,
There are rumors that Yuzaki-chan is a candy-flashing reworking,
When I first appeared in Yuzaki-chan's room, I said it was nice to meet you, but Aira was not there.
I was not there.
I was not that concerned about it, but I was just thrusting the idea that there might be some kind of a guess,
Let me elaborate on that fact.
I like everyone.
But now I'm interested in Hama-chan.
Really?
Me too.
I like everyone. You know I like you guys, right? I like you all.
We've been talking on LINE so much.
Eeeee!
Hama-chan, is there anyone you like that's been on your mind lately?
I like you, I like you, I like you.
I like her.
Really?
Could it be that Suika-kun is also Daikoku?
Oh no.
You mean he's a big black guy?
Don't tell us.
Well, I knew he was Daikoku, but he's not my favorite right now.Hey, um, I knew Daikoku so, but I'm not guessing now.
Oh no.
Awkward, awkward.
But you know what? Yuka-chan.
Kojima-san is a little bit like that.
I was saying that now.
Oh no.
You said a lot of things.
Want to say it?
Go ahead.
Today?
You too, Hama-chan.
Aaaaah!
Could it be, could it be?
I want to know as much as Mototaka-chan.
Aaaaah!
I myself am a Mototaka-chan guesser.
That's great.
Come back anytime, Yuuka-chan.
Eh, I should go back.
I'm sorry.
Are you coming back too, Daikoku?
I'm counting on you.
Even just a little?
I love you.
I really love you.
I love it when you put a light on my room.
Oh, no.
There's a gag about giving people nicknames.
What's that?
I'm used to it.
I give them nicknames.
He's laughing by himself.
It's the worst.
I'm sweating a lot.
I'm sweating and there's some kind of weird sweat floating around.
It's bad.
Is it okay?
It's funny.
Daikoku, Yusu, Kii.
Ooooooooooo!
Yay!
No matter what kind of gag we do, it's for the sake of the gag that slides so beautifully between us,
I was hoping that Yu-chan could use it as a self-introduction gag.
Is it okay if I do it now?
Let's let the senpai do it.
That would suck.
I'll never get it.
I'm sorry, I'm at the center.
I'll never understand.
Daikoku, Daikaku, Yusu, Kii.
What did you say?
What did you say, Daishaku?
I'm on the phone.
Daishaku, Daikoku, Yusu, Kii.
Excuse me, I'd like to send them on their way.
Please applaud.
Let's go.
Daihaku, Daikoku, Yusu, Kii.
We won!
You!
Are you going to do it?
I don't know.
Are you okay? Before this.
Are you okay?
I want it before the show.
Daikoku-san is going to collaborate with Michi this time.
I'm so happy!
I'm so happy.
Can I ask you one thing?
I'm going to collaborate with Michi at the rehearsal.
I had a thought.
Yusu-chan doesn't make eye contact with me at all.
Huh? More!
More!
I wanted to make more eye contact too.
I wish you would come more often.
Actually, I couldn't make eye contact at all even if I wanted to because of the tight chain.
I just step on my feet.
I really can't do this.
Come on!
Come more!
Go further!
Can't you go!
You can't go!
You okay? This is before the show.
No problem.
We'll go first.We will go first.
Wakka!
Yuka-chan, I don't know what hit me right now.
I don't know.
Well, Yuka-chan.
Please don't get stuck again.
I was so surprised.
Sakai No Aoi
Jessie & Kyoki Yeah!
I knew I loved it and everything вы
I'm so happy!
I wanted to abrir from the students.
I knew all about it.
I'm so happy!
Pond flesh
I just wanted to make sure you were okay.
It was fun.
There were some things I couldn't get right.
It felt so good.
It felt good.
Now, doctor, you're embarrassing me with this delivery.
Let's hold it down.
I'll get it under control.
That's good.
It's done!
Next, the one who did it,
Yuuzuki-chan!
Amazing!
You look great!
So nice!
I knew I had to do it,
I had to do it for sure.
It was amazing.
And I was told that the winner of the award would receive a present,
I'm going to send a dinner with them next time!
Yay!
Let's go out to dinner!
Can I?
Can I complicate things?
No, no, no. There's the worst person in the world.
Let's all go! Let's go, let's go, let's go!
I love you guys! Let's go!
But first things first,
Well, let's all go together, and I'll be the one who gets pissed off.
That's fine!
Yuzu!
I'll decide then!
Okay, I'll hold this.
Let's go! So.
Let's go! Let's go!
I really, really wanted to go!
We're so good!
Nothing more.
Okay! OK! Sorry!
Well, congratulations!
Thank you very much!
Nothing happened.
Oh, shit!
Seriously.
I was so nervous!
That was scary.
I was nervous.
Thank you so much!
Good luck!
Congratulations!
Well, that's why it was the senpai bukkomi championship.
This time, you know, Yuzu won the championship.
Thank you very much!
You are really good at this!
Yuzu is really good at this kind of thing.
You're really good at this!
This is how I've made my life.
It's the only thing I've got going for me.
I've worked so hard to get here.
I see.
Ameftasy made it through.
This is the team that got me into the starting stage.
That's for sure.
So your audition was high.
At first, you know, because it was like that.
But I got pretty emotional.
I see!
It went up so much.
I think it's funny.
I'm glad you cleaned up the yuzu.
That was good.
One more time and you're probably beat.One more time and you're probably fucked.
I didn't do everything.
But it's just something that comes naturally.
I guess I didn't do it.
At the end, you know, it's a little bit...
I'd like to see it again.
It was playing a little bit.
You might not have seen much of it.
Aya, can I ask you a question?
It's crazy.
It's okay, it's okay.
It's not right.
You were chosen, but it's time to go.
I'd love to get some of Aya's emotional material.
Then let me do it when you send Oshiro on his way.
Can I ask you to give it your all?
I'm on it.
Yuzu to send Oshiro home!
Emotion!
Yuzu, are you beautiful?
Involving, involving.
See you all next time.
Bye bye!